<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ADESPL</string>
    <string name="laploan">A loan against property (LAP) or Mortgage Loan is a secured loan that is sanctioned against the asset pledged as collateral. This asset can either be an owned land, a house, or any other commercial premises. The asset remains as collateral with the lender until the entire loan against property amount is repaid.LAP (Loan against Property) is processed against a property that is already on borrower’s name. LAP is taken for both the personal and business usage. In this case, the mortgaged security is already owned by the borrower. As a DSA we provide LAP or Mortgage loan in a very short time with reasonable ROI and documentation. If you need LAP or Mortgage Loan you can reach us.</string>
    <string name="carloan">Dreaming of owning a car? Adorable Economics Solution Pvt. Ltd. Car Loan aims to ensure that you drive around the city in your own vehicle! Avail a car loan, or opt for a pre-approved car loan, and get the best interest rates. Apply for an Adorable Economics Solution Pvt. Ltd. New Car Loan and make your dream of owning a car come true. Adorable Economics Solution Pvt. Ltd. offers Car Loans up to 100% of the on-road price of the car, with attractive interest rates. Apply now for approval and faster processing of your car loan.</string>
    <string name="homeloan">A home loan is a secured loan that is obtained to purchase a property by offering it as collateral. Home loans offer high-value funding at economical interest rates and for long tenors. They are repaid through EMIs. After repayment, the property’s title is transferred back to the borrower. As a DSA we provide Home Loan to customer at a nominal documentation with reasonable rate of interest at minimum 7.5 % p.a. to maximum 16% p.a.</string>
    <string name="businessloan">A business loan is a loan specifically intended for business purposes. To grow your dream business bigger if you need financial help, there we are for the support of a perfect Business Loan for you. These customized loans can give your business the much-needed boost to help your enterprise scale new heights with enhanced competitiveness and profitability. To grow your business fast we provide Business Loan from our shortlisted and reputed organization so that you can get it in a nominal time and nominal documentation with a reasonable rate of interest at minimum 8.5% p.a. to maximum 20% p.a.</string>
    <string name="personalloan">A personal loan is an amount of money you can borrow to use for a variety of purposes. Personal Loans are the best way to meet your expenses during an emergency or fund any unplanned situation in life. Whether you are planning your next dream vacation with your loved ones or want to get funds for our child’s marriage, a Personal Loan offers double benefits of quick access to funds and zero need for collateral. Personal Loans have emerged as a great way to finance purchases that otherwise would have been challenging with a regular paycheck. For those who are looking for an instant Personal Loan online, we have great offers for Personal Loans.</string>
</resources>